OSAGIE OSAHON JOSHUA

Web/ App Developer

DATE OF BIRTH: February 14th 2003

ABOUT ME

Solution-driven web developer adapt at contributing to highly collaborative environment and finding solutions. Proven experience developing consumer-focused websites using HTML, CSS, NODE.JS, and JavaScript. Good knowledge of the best practices for web design, user experience and speed.

PERSONAL SKILLS

- Clear Comunication
- Teamwork
- Time Management
- Creativity
- Android applications
- Programming Languages
- Management
- Multitasking

LANGUAGES

English ****

**** Pidgin English

Yoruba

+2347044776239 +2347082946076

osagiejoshua16@gmail.com

🔾 Washgate, Jahi apartment, Lapaloma Residence, Jahi 1, Abuja, Nigeria

Sex: Male

EDUCATION

2018 - 2021 West African Examinations Council (WAEC) Precious Gift International School

Basic Education Certification Examination 2014-2016

Government Secondary School Nyanya Abuja

First School Leaving Certificate 2008-2013

Mater Dei International School

EXPERIENCE

2017 - 2019 Sales and Repairs of computers

Star tech Best Limited Customer support, sales representative, repairs of computer parts, installs, and troubleshoots different types of issues affecting computer systems servers, or networks.

2021 - Till Date

Programming.

Bizzmarrow Tech Hub Write, modify, and test code and scripts that allow computer software applications and to function properly.

INTEREST

- Blogging
- Charity
- Traveling
- Coding

PROJECTS

- Pinterest Business Website, Created with React (Copyright)
- Wells Fargo Banking, Created with HTML & CSS (Copyright)
- Tom Ford Clothing Website, Created with HTML & CSS (Copyright)
- Bitcoin website used (Coin Geko API), Created with React, Java Script.
- Blog website Created with HTML & CSS, Boostrap, node js, Express, Mongodb & Ejs.
- Local Music Application, Created with React Native, Expo Go, JavaScript, Expo cli and more.
- Online food store website created with react, bootstrap and CSS

REFERENCE

AVAILABLE ON REQUEST.

CERTIFICATE

COMPUTER NETWORKING 2019

COMPUTER PROGRAMMING 2023